# VERONIKA HARBACHOVA

Austin, TX | veronika.har@hotmail.com

# **Profile Summary**

Linguist turned web developer blends soft skills of adaptability and openmindedness with hard skills of web design. Cross-functional collaboration with tech teams and successful experience of working as a part of one. Experience in logistics honed my problem-solving, analytical and leadership skills.

## Education

## **Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development**

CareerFoundry | 01/2019 - 11/2019

- 300+ hours of training/mentoring with industry leading Front-End and Senior Full-Stack Web Developer.
- Intensive project-based training program with a focus on JavaScript, HTML, CSS and most prominent libraries, frameworks and tools;
- To see my skills in action, visit <a href="https://veronikaharbachova.netlify.com/">https://veronikaharbachova.netlify.com/</a>

#### **MA** in Linguistics

Dalian University of Technology | 09/2008 - 07/2011

#### **BA in Linguistics**

Belarusian State University | 09/2003 - 06/2008

## **Employment History**

#### Wallenborn Transports S.A – Luxembourg, Luxembourg

Supply Chain Specialist | 02/2015 - 07/2016

- ✓ Provided customer support and account management for Qatar Airlines EU freight handling. Established strong relationship with QA office in Atlanta.
- ✓ Analyzed the company's internal S&OP software (AS-TRANS) and cooperated with an outsourced development team on its improvement;

### Lear Corporation - Shanghai, China

Supply Chain Specialist | 11/2013 - 06/2014

- ✓ Lead Logistics Network Optimization for China Seating: identified potential of 20-25% (\$300k annually) savings;
- ✓ Supported LEAR Malaysia Supply Chain recovery;

### **Generation\_P** – *Minsk*, *Belarus*

XSLT developer / Assistant Team-Leader | 09/2007 – 08/2008

- ✓ Achieved full technical competency in 3 months without any prior experience (CVS repo; PAROS (POST/GET); Oxygen+Eclipse; XML etc);
- ✓ Assistant Team-Leader supervised team performing patch-and-release responsibilities and negotiated business solutions with foreign customers.

#### Skills

**HTML** 

**CSS** 

JavaScript

React.js

Node.js

jQuery

Redux

**React Native** 

**PWA** 

**APIs** 

Photoshop

Bootstrap

Responsive Design

TDD

## **Toolkit**

NPM

TypeScript

Sass

Jest/Enzyme

CodePen

Git (GitHub)

Chrome Developer

Tools

## Languages

English

Russian

Italian

**Mandarin Chinese** 

Ukranian

Belarusian